http://www.adobegallery.com/page/privacy-policy

Adobe Gallery
221 Canyon Road
Santa Fe, New Mexico 87501
Phone (505) 955-0550Fax (866) 919-9506www.adobegallery.cominfo@adobegallery.com
SearchContactBlogAboutHelpLoginJoin
New AcquisitionsSouthwest Indian PotteryContemporaryHistoricPrehistoricFigurinesKachina/Katsina DollsZuniHopiNative American PaintingsDrawingsPaintingsPrintsNative American BasketsSouthwest Indian JewelryBelts and BucklesBola TiesBraceletsButtons and Conchas Complete SetsEarringsNecklaces PendantsPinsRingsSilver Objects SilverwareToolsWestern ArtDrawingsPaintingsPrintsArts and Crafts FurnitureFurnitureAccessoriesBooksOtherBeadworkClothingDance Paraphernalia Navajo Textiles & Blankets Pueblo DrumsPueblo Textiles Bronze SculptureOther ItemsSpecial ExhibitsSearchContactBlogAboutHelpLoginJoin
New AcquisitionsSouthwest Indian PotteryContemporaryHistoricPrehistoricFigurinesKachina/Katsina DollsZuniHopiNative American PaintingsDrawingsPaintingsPrints
Native American BasketsSouthwest Indian JewelryBelts and BucklesBola TiesBraceletsButtons and Conchas Complete SetsEarringsNecklaces PendantsPinsRingsSilver Objects SilverwareToolsWestern ArtDrawingsPaintingsPrintsArts and Crafts FurnitureFurnitureAccessoriesBooksOtherBeadworkClothingDance Paraphernalia Navajo Textiles & Blankets Pueblo DrumsPueblo Textiles Bronze SculptureOther ItemsSpecial Exhibits
Privacy Policy
Thank you for exploring the Adobe Gallery website (adobegallery.com).These Terms of Use govern your use and access to this site.  We may change, update, delete or add to these terms over time.  By accessing and using this site, you agree to these Terms of Use, all policies with this site (including our return policy), and all changes or modifications to the foregoing.
Privacy Policy
We respect the privacy of our customers and encourage you to read our Privacy Policy Statement so that you may make an informed decision about using our site.
Privacy Policy Statement:To protect the privacy of our clients (customers and members), client personal information and e-mail address will not be provided to any third parties. Client information will only be used for program maintenance and marketing purposes, to improve on product offerings and services provided by Adobe Gallery and so that Adobe Gallery may provide other promotional information and opportunities about Adobe Gallery and adobegallery.com to the client.
What do you use my information for?
Your personal information is only used for administering adobegallery.com and the My Adobe Gallery program. This includes tracking purchases and consignments so you can review them, sending you communications and promotions via email and your home address, and using the preferences you registered to ensure we are communicating with you how, when and about what things are of interest to you.
Adobe Gallery
221 Canyon Road Santa Fe, NM 87501
505.955.0550
info@adobegallery.com
Adobe Gallery Hours: 10am to 5pm DailyClosed Sundays
New AcquisitionsSouthwest Indian PotteryKachina/Katsina DollsNative American PaintingsNative American BasketsSouthwest Indian JewelryEuropean American ArtArts and Crafts FurnitureBooksOtherSpecial Exhibits
Member LoginHomeAdobe Gallery BlogContact UsAbout UsHelpSearchPrivacy PolicyReturn PolicyCopyrightReport a Problem
Join
Login
Site content ©1998-2020 Adobe Gallery. Adobe Gallery reserves reproduction rights to all images and content on this website.
